clickreport.com 2010-12-15

# DoogleOnDuty - Click Fraud Detection and Monitoring

## Privacy Policy

##### Effective Date: 7/31/2007

#### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

DoogleOnDuty is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. DoogleOnDuty collects information from our users when they register for this service.

#### REGISTRATION

In order to register for DoogleOnDuty service, a user must first complete a short registration form. During this process a user is required to give personal details such as their full name, phone number, email, credit card, and address details. This information is used to validate the authenticity of the user registering for the service. Credit Card Numbers are collected from our users to charge them for our services.

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. This company does not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we at DoogleOnDuty are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statement of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

This website also contains a link to a Live Chat function that is hosted by one of our service providers. Because this is hosted on a Third Party's web site, the information that is collected here, such as you email address, name, and phone number, is governed by the service provider's web site and not by DoogleOnDuty.

#### COOKIES

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. For example, if you are using Microsoft Internet Explorer please follow the directions on the following web site: <http://support.microsoft.com/kb/283185>

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See "Third Party Advertisers."

#### PRIVACY

Any information collected by DoogleOnDuty during the sign-up process is not sold, rented, leased, or distributed to any third party organization.

#### SECURITY

This website takes every precaution to protect our user's information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices, every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customer's information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked security door. All other users account information is protected by a password authentication process. Our servers have the latest industry standard firewall protection and are constantly monitored 24 hours a day. If you have any questions about security at our website, you can send an email to [security@doogleonduty.com](mailto:security@doogleonduty.com). DoogleOnDuty uses SSL Encryption to protect the sensitive information our users submit to our website, such as their credit card numbers.

#### CORRECTION/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your post code or zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, our users may email us at [sales@doogleonduty.com](mailto:sales@doogleonduty.com) or call us at (978) 747-6694 to have their information changed or deleted.

#### LEGAL DISCLAIMER

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site

#### BUSINESS TRANSITIONS

In the event DoogleOnDuty goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

#### NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what our policy is at any moment in time. If at any time we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

WebForza, Inc.  
89 Main Street  
Andover, MA 01810  
United States  
Telephone (978) 747-6694
